<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.vdr.recordings" name="VDR Recordings" version="1.0.0" provider-name="Markus Ehrnsperger">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="resources/lib/addon.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.library" library="resources/lib/contextMenu.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>Copyright: GNU GPLv3</license>
    <forum></forum>
    <website>https://github.com/MarkusEh/plugin.video.vdr.recordings/wiki</website>
    <email></email>
    <source>https://github.com/MarkusEh/plugin.video.vdr.recordings</source>
    <news>
v1.0.0
- Language support
- Improve performance
- Support https://github.com/MarkusEh/vdr-plugin-tvscraper
- Improve support of KODI libraries
- Add plugin icon and screenshots
v0.4.0
- Support KODI 19, and stop support of KODI 18
v0.3.6
- Recordings are now listed in the same hierarchy as VDR
v0.3.5
- add container refresh command
v0.3.4
- fix move videos with xbmcvfs
v0.3.3
- ignore missing index files (now also working with xbmcvfs)
v0.3.2
- if the recording folder (*.rec) has an invalid format, the recording is still displayed with date 1960-01-01, 0:00:00. There will be an error message in the log
v0.3.1
- typo in vdrrecordingfolder.py: fixed xbmcvfs.exist -> xbmcvfs.exists
v0.3.0
- support xbmcvfs
v0.2.4
- ignore missing index files
v0.2.3
- change: Delete now permanently deletes a recording. There is a confirmation popup
- new: Move of recordings
v0.2.2
- support nun-integer framerates
- support marks.txt
v0.2.1
- Also support marks.vdr
v0.2.0
- Support marks, create comskip file
v0.1.3
- Movies: Support year
v0.1.2
- TV shows: To aviod issue with KODI scrapper, TV shows are now flat (no subfolders).
- Add search entry in context menu  
v0.1.1  
- Added support for KODI libraries
    </news>
    <assets>
        <icon>resources/vdr-logo_bigPlayRecordings.png</icon>
        <fanart></fanart>
        <banner></banner>
        <clearlogo></clearlogo>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshot00001.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshot00010.png</screenshot>
        <screenshot>resources/screenshot00011.png</screenshot>
    </assets>
    <reuselanguageinvoker>true</reuselanguageinvoker>
    <summary lang="da_DK">Afspil VDR-optagelser</summary>
    <summary lang="de_DE">VDR Aufzeichnungen wiedergeben</summary>
    <summary lang="en_GB">Play VDR recordings</summary>
    <summary lang="it_IT">Riproduci registrazioni VDR</summary>
    <summary lang="pl_PL">Odtwarzaj nagrania VDR</summary>
    <description lang="ca_ES">Si utilitzes Klaus Schmidingers VDR http://www.tvdr.de per crear gravacions de TV, podeu utilitzar aquest connector per veure-les a KODI.[CR]Necessiteu accedir al sistema de fitxers on s&apos;emmagatzemen les gravacions VDR, per exemple, utilitzant NFS. No cal executar un VDR durant la reproducció de les gravacions amb aquest connector.</description>
    <description lang="da_DK">Hvis du bruger Klaus Schmidingers VDR (http://www.tvdr.de) for at oprette tv -optagelser, kan du bruge dette plugin til at se dem i Kodi.[CR]Du har brug for adgang til filsystemet, hvor VDR -optagelserne er gemt, f.eks. gennem NFS. En kørende VDR er ikke påkrævet under afspilning af optagelserne med dette plugin.</description>
    <description lang="de_DE">Abspielen von TV Aufzeichnungen, die mit Klaus Schmidingers VDR http://www.tvdr.de erstellt wurden. [CR]Voraussetzung: KODI benötigt Zugriff auf das Dateisystem mit den Aufzeichnungen, z.B. über NFS. Zur Wiedergabe der Aufzeichnungen mit diesem Plugin wird VDR nicht benötigt.</description>
    <description lang="en_GB">If you use Klaus Schmidingers VDR http://www.tvdr.de to create TV recorings, you can use this plugin to watch them in KODI.[CR]You do need access to the file system where the VDR recordings are stored, e.g. using NFS. A running VDR is not required during playback of the recordings with this plugin.</description>
    <description lang="it_IT">Se utilizzi Klaus Schmidingers VDR http://www.tvdr.de per creare registrazioni TV, puoi utilizzare questo plugin per guardarle in KODI.[CR]È necessario accedere al file system in cui sono archiviate le registrazioni VDR, ad es. usando NFS. Non è necessario un VDR in esecuzione durante la riproduzione delle registrazioni con questo plugin.</description>
    <description lang="pl_PL">Jeśli używasz VDR http://www.tvdr.de Klausa Schmidingera do tworzenia nagrań telewizyjnych, możesz użyć tej wtyczki, aby oglądać je w KODI.[CR]Potrzebujesz dostępu do systemu plików, w którym przechowywane są nagrania VDR, np. za pomocą NFS. Działający VDR nie jest wymagany podczas odtwarzania nagrań za pomocą tej wtyczki.</description>
  </extension>
</addon>
